jesus-loves-you.org 2017-06-28

# Privacy @ The Hunger Site

CharityUSA, owners and operators of the GreaterGood family of websites, has created this privacy policy to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices. CharityUSA does not sell, rent, trade, or share Personal Information with third parties except as disclosed within this privacy policy.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

This privacy policy covers the following:

>   
> **GreaterGood**   
> [The Hunger Site](http://thehungersite.com/) and store and blog   
> [The Breast Cancer Site](http://thebreastcancersite.com/) and store and blog   
> [The Animal Rescue Site](http://theanimalrescuesite.com/) and store and blog   
> [The Veterans Site](http://theveteranssite.com/) and store and blog   
> [The Autism Site](http://theautismsite.com/) and store and blog   
> [The Alzheimer's Site](http://thealzheimerssite.com/) and store and blog   
> [The Diabetes Site](http://thediabetessite.com/) and store and blog   
> [The Literacy Site](http://theliteracysite.com/) and store and blog   
> [The Earth Site](http://blog.theearthsite.com/) blog and store   
> [The Rainforest Site](http://therainforessite.com/) and store and blog   
> **GreaterGood Kids**   
> **Great Life Publishing**   

* * *

## Free Daily Click

Clicking on the "Click Here to Give" button on the home page of The Animal Rescue Site, The Breast Cancer Site, The Hunger Site, and all of our other Click-to-Give sites is free to the visitor. 100% of the money from sponsor advertising is given to the charity partners of each site by GreaterGood.org. You are not required to provide any personal information to visit the GreaterGood sites or to make your daily, free click.

Site visitors may also help protect animals, people, and our planet by signing petitions and taking other actions at our sites. Site visitors may voluntarily provide personal information to sign a "Take Action!" petition, share a story, photograph, testimonial or other comment with the GreaterGood community, sign up for an e-newsletter or click reminder emails, or participate in other site activities as we offer them. See below for how we use this information.

## Take Action! Petitions

Signing a "Take Action!" petition gives you a way to impact public policy in ways that connect to the core issues of our Click-to-Give sites. When you sign a petition at any one of the GreaterGood sites, you are required to provide certain personal information such as name, email address, and sometimes street address so it can be shared with the target of the campaign in order to influence the outcome of legislation or change policies in order to help people or animals. This personal information is required to validate your campaign signature. All personal information you provide when signing a petition or participating in a petition, including name, address, city, state, country, and comments are considered public information and will be provided to the target of the campaign (for example, sending a letter and petition to the Surgeon General). Specific targets for a petition will be clearly identified within each petition. Your city, state, country, and comments will also be visible on the Click-to-Give site(s) associated with the petition. Your name will also be visible on the site unless you have checked the "Do not display my name" checkbox at the time of signing. We will not display street or email addresses entered into the proper "Email" or "Address" fields during signing. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these petitions.

CharityUSA hosts two kinds of petitions: petitions sponsored by one of our Click-to-Give sites (such as The Animal Rescue Site), and petitions sponsored by nonprofits. At the time of signing you will have an opportunity to indicate whether or not you wish to receive communication from any third-party nonprofit sponsor of the campaign. If you do not opt-out of such communications, CharityUSA will send your contact information to the third-party nonprofit sponsoring the campaign. If you opt-out of receiving such online offers, CharityUSA will not share your name, email address, or other signing information with the nonprofit sponsor. Each petition signing also subscribes you to our "Take Action!" email list. We provide unsubscribe options with each and every email sent in this manner. This is also summarized in the "Choice and Opt-out" section.

## Share Your Story/Visitor Testimonials/Comments/Reviews

When we post visitor stories, testimonials, comments, or reviews on our web site, these may contain personal information such as name, city, and state. We obtain consent in the submission form prior to posting the story, testimonial, comment, or review. At the time of submission you may also choose the "Do not display my name" option, which will replace your name with "Anonymous". If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [customerservice@greatergood.com](mailto:customerservice@greatergood.com). Please note that external software (such as "Googlebot") periodically browses our sites and publishes "snapshots" of what it indexes to the Internet. We cannot remove or edit these "snapshots", only the content currently displaying on our own sites.

* * *

## Communications from the Site

### Email Product or Petition to a Friend

If you choose to email a product description to a friend, we will ask you for your name and email address, and for your recipient's name and email address. If you choose to send a petition description to a friend, only the friend's email address is required. We will automatically send your chosen recipient(s) a one-time email to view the product or petition. CharityUSA does not store, sell, trade or otherwise use any name or email address you share here for any purpose other than to deliver your message.

### E-newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our e-newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send a periodic email to you. We provide unsubscribe options with each and every email sent in this manner. This is also summarized in the "Choice and Opt-out" section.

### Special Offers and Updates

Once you've shopped with us in one of our do-good stores, we will periodically send you information on products, services, special deals, and promotions. You may opt-out of receiving these types of communications during checkout. This is also summarized in the "Choice and Opt-out" section. Subscribers are the first to be notified of start dates of major sales and other promotions, and periodically receive subscriber-exclusive offers which are great deals and free products available only to subscribers who continue to receive our updates.

### Service-related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

### Accounts

You do not need an account to make a free daily click or to purchase anything from our store. If you choose to create an account, we will ask for and store your name, email address, and a password to give you access to and to protect your account. We also give you an opportunity during checkout to save your billing and shipping addresses in order to provide a speedier and more convenient checkout experience in the future. We do not store any credit card data in your account.

### Shopping

When you purchase something at a GreaterGood store, we request certain personal information from you on our order form. During checkout, you will be asked to give your billing address, shipping address, phone number and email address. We use your email address to confirm your order, and in case there are any problems with your order. Phone numbers are occasionally used to communicate with you about your order only. Credit card information is encrypted and used for order billing only: we do not save your credit card information. During checkout you will be able to sign up for special offers and updates, an email sent approximately once a week. You may unsubscribe at any time. Instructions for unsubscribing are included in each email sent.

CharityUSA may provide your personal information to third parties that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or a payment processor to bill you for goods and services. These third party service providers do not retain, share, store, or otherwise use your personal information for any other purpose other than to provide services to us, and are prohibited from marketing to you.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. If CharityUSA is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our sites of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

### Gifts That Give More™

When you make an online donation via GreaterGood.org's Gift That Gives More™ program, we share your personal information with our nonprofit, independent partner, GreaterGood.org. You will receive your U.S. tax receipt from GreaterGood.org upon completing your donation and may also receive direct donation appeals from GreaterGood.org. 100% of the money you contribute via a Gift That Gives More™ is given to GreaterGood.org to be used for the purposes specified; we even cover bank and credit card charges in order to ensure that 100% goes to the charitable purpose you intend. Information about which organizations are granted money contributed through the Gift That Gives More™ program as well as other grants is available on the GreaterGood.org website.

* * *

## Links/Social Media Widgets/Electronic Log Files/Tracking Technologies/Local Storage Objects/Retargeting

Each of our Web sites contain links to other Web sites, including sponsor sites and other philanthropic sites. CharityUSA is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites and encourages you to review these companies' privacy policies.

### Social Media Widgets

Our Web sites include social media features such as the Facebook "Like" button and widgets, "Share this" button, and other interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our sites. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Electronic Log Files

As is true of most sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in electronic log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information. We use this information to understand how our websites are used to better meet the needs of our visitors and customers. We use IP addresses to identify and block malicious behavior like click fraud or denial of service attacks.

### Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, and scripts are used by CharityUSA and our partners, affiliates, analytics and service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart to save your shopping for a return visit, to save your order ID until a successful order authorization, and, in future, we may use cookies to store your click history to show you the good you've accomplished by visiting and taking action around the sites.

You do not have to accept cookies in order to make your free, daily click and have your click count, or to shop with us. You can control the use of cookies from your browser. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

### Local Storage Objects (LSOs)

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third party partners who provide certain features on our site or display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML5 and Flash LSOs to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash cookies, please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

### Behavioral Targeting/Retargeting

CharityUSA partners with a third party ad network to both display advertising on our own Web sites and to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partners use cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personal information about your activities on this and other Web sites in order to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests, and to provide you relevant advertising through retargeting when you leave our sites. If you do not want this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here <http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/>, or by using the [NAI opt-out mechanism](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Please note that this does not opt you out of being served advertising -- you will continue to see general ads that are not targeted to your interests.

Due to technological limitations at this time, CharityUSA does not respond to browser Do Not Track signals.

CharityUSA constantly uses aggregate and non-personally recognizable data about our customers both internally and using external providers, including Facebook and Google, to try to understand customer concerns and provide better products and promotions. We segment our data and email lists by issue area of concern, and also by type of product purchased, recency, frequency, and monetary value of purchase, which charitable gifts have been given, and other demographic and geographic data.

We don't sell or rent our email lists. We do use our email lists to create profiles of our shoppers and clickers in order to market to similar people. We use outside groups, including Facebook, to help us in this effort, but we don't allow outside groups to contact our shoppers or customers. These contractors help us create profiles of our shoppers, so we can market to similar people on other sites. This marketing is subject to the privacy policies of whatever site we are buying these ads on, and is not subject to our privacy policies.

We will use information that we have about your shopping or clicking behavior to provide you better quality offers and promotions, and to help us understand and serve our customers better.

* * *

## Security

Your comfort and security while shopping with us are important. We have multiple ways of protecting our customers:

  * We do not save or store your credit card number. 

For your protection, we do not keep your credit card information on file. Your billing information is securely transmitted to our payment processor one time only. Our security measures and internal processes are designed to ensure that your billing information is kept secure while we process your order.

  * We use encrypted URLs for our shopping cart and checkout process. Encrypted URLs begin with an "https" instead of the plain-text protocol of "http".
  * Our site security keys use the highest industry standard for encryption.
  * We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [customerservice@greatergood.com](mailto:customerservice@greatergood.com).
  * You can read more on how to shop online safely [here](http://www.microsoft.com/security/online-privacy/finances-rules.aspx).

Please note: Your credit card statement will show the name of the store where your order originated.

> GreaterGood Shop   
> The Hunger Site   
> The Breast Cancer Site   
> The Animal Rescue Site   
> The Veterans Site   
> The Autism Site   
> The Alzheimer's Site   
> The Diabetes Site   
> The Literacy Site   
> The Eatrrh Site   
> The Rainforest Site   
> Creative Kidstuff   
> Sensational Beginnings   
> Coupaw   
> Doggyloot   
> RescueBox   
> Global Girlfriend   
> Sasa Designs   
> Hope Faith Love   
> Pink Ribbon Store 

If we cannot identify which storefront you entered through, charges will appear on your statement as CharityUSA.com, LLC.

Ordering online with us is secure and easy. If you have any concerns about ordering online, please feel free to place your order with our customer service department by phone. Hours are 8:00 am to 7:00 pm (Eastern Time), Monday through Friday. You may call us toll-free within the U.S. and Canada at 1-888-355-4321. To contact us from outside the U.S. and Canada, please call 206-268-5401.

### Collection of Personal Information from Children

CharityUSA does not knowingly collect individually identifiable information from or about children under 13. If CharityUSA later learns that we have personal information about a child under 13, we will take steps to remove that child's information from our databases. If you have questions or concerns, please contact us at 206-268-5401 or by email: [customerservice@greatergood.com](mailto:customerservice@greatergood.com).

### Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting personal information

If your personal information changes, you may contact us to amend, correct, or delete it at [customerservice@greatergood.com](mailto:customerservice@greatergood.com). We will respond to your request within 1 business day.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Choice/Opt-out

We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your personal information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive marketing material from us following your order, you can opt-out during the checkout process.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter or other promotional communications, please let us know by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each newsletter and communication, or by contacting us at:

GreaterGood Customer Service   
One Union Square   
600 University Street, Suite 1000   
Seattle, WA 98101-4107   
U.S.A.   

U.S. and Canada: 1-888-355-4321   
Outside the U.S. and Canada: 206-268-5401   
Customer Service hours are 8:00 am to 7:00 pm (Eastern Time), Monday through Friday.

You will be notified if your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider other than as specified in this policy, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. Although there are no plans to do this presently, if this ever occurs, an opt-out will be provided to you before any personal information is shared, so it is always your choice when information is provided to a third party.

### Changes to this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by means of a notice on this Site or by email prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 6, 2016.
